sakhr.com 2011-08-21

# Sakhr Privacy

This Policy applies to all of the products, Services and websites offered by Sakhr Software Company or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, "Services"). In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post separate privacy notices to describe how particular Services process personal information.

**Information we collect and how we use it:**  
In order to provide our Services, we may collect the following types of information:

**Information you provide** \- By using our Services, including accessing our Services via phone or SMS, we may ask you for your present location, destination location, phone numbers, or other information. When you sign up for an account or other service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). We maintain such information on secure servers. For some of our Services in which you request that we send information to third parties, your phone number or other identifying information may be displayed to such parties. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information we gather or from third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our Services.

**Cookies** \- When you visit our websites or use Sakhr Software Company, we may send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Some features and Services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**Log information** \- When you use Sakhr Software Company, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These servers may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. Sakhr Software Company also recognizes you by your mobile phone number and/or email address and logs the information you send on our servers.

**User communications** \- When you send email or other communication to Sakhr Software Company, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our Services. Some messages (including SMS messages) may automatically be sent to you from our service.

**Affiliated sites** \- We offer some of our Services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Sakhr Software Company in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. We only process personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific Services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

Providing our products and Services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising; Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our Services; Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and Developing new Services. Sakhr Software Company may process personal information to provide our own Services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

**Choices for personal information**  
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use personal information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. You can decline to submit personal information to any of our Services, in which case we may not be able to provide those Services to you.

**Information sharing**  
Sakhr Software Company only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Sakhr Software Company in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Sakhr Software Company, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Sakhr Software Company becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information which does not identify you individually.

**Changes to this policy**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Policy changes on this page.

Effective Date: May 20th, 2009
